beyond-gaming.net 2019-01-22

# Privacy Policy – Beyond Gaming

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information (PII)’ is being used online. PII, as used in the United States and International privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from visitors to our website and/or app?

## PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Beyond-Gaming.net collects personal information during (i) personal profile, contest or sweepstakes registration; (ii) subscription registration for services that require a subscription; (iii) certain surveys or polls conducted on our web site.  Personal information includes, among other things, a user’s name, date of birth, gender, email address or other internet address (collectively referred to as ‘personal information’). In addition, registration is required and personal information is collected in certain other portions of the service in which users specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, blog postings (ie chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, information requests or voting.

## NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

In addition to the use of personal information to operate the site, Beyond Gaming.net may also gather non-personally identifiable information, which may be used by Beyond Gaming. Generally ‘non-personally identifiable information’ means information that is collected through ‘traffic data’ and may entail the use of ‘cookies’, ‘IP addresses’ or other numeric codes used to identify a computer or monitor how a user accesses a site. This non-personally identifiable information helps us determine how our customers use the site so that we can improve our site and ensure it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of our users as possible. We also provide statistical ‘ratings’ information to our partners about how our users collectively, use the site. We do this so that they too can understand how people use our site in order for them to make business decisions directed towards providing you, the user, with the best possible experience. This information is also used to generate advertising rates and may be shared with advertisers, sponsors, and other Beyond Gaming.net corporate partners. We may also provide an advertising partner insight as to how long a user views a page to better determine relevant advertising content.

## How do we use your information?

Beyond Gaming.net reserves the right to use, store, provide or disclose personal information collected during your individual visits to our web site and the information that you give us, such as, your name, email address, date of birth or gender. In most cases our use or disclosure will be an added benefit to you. This data will be used to determine relevant gaming content for you, our users giving you the best possible experience on our website. You may contact us at any time and instruct us to remove your information from future mailings. Any use, storage, provision or disclosure of your personal information by Beyond Gaming.net will be made in strict compliance with any applicable laws.  In addition, you will be provided the option to opt-out from any subscription mail services that you receive. We may also disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to applicable law or comply with legal processes.

## Children under the age of 13 years

We do not encourage children to provide us with any personally identifiable information. We ask that children (12 years of age and under) do NOT submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor under the age of 13 years, please use our services only with the approval of, and under the supervision of your parents or legal guardian(s). We support the guidelines and regulatory requirements provided in the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

  * How do we protect visitor information?
  * We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
  * We use regular Malware Scanning.
  * We do not use an SSL certificate.
  * Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow this). Cookies enable the sites’ or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to determine which articles are popular, allowing us to release more content within that category to improve your user experience and service.

## WE MAY USE COOKIES TO:

  * keep track of advertisements.
  * compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled but this won’t affect the your experience however it could result in some features not functioning properly.  
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It’s important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking in order to improve user experience and service.

We have implemented the following:

  * Third Party advertising links
  * Mailchimp email subscription services
  * Facebook tracking pixel
  * Amazon associates program
  * Google services (Google AdSense, Google Analytics, Google +1, Google Remarketing)
  * Third party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not however include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, as long as these parties agree to keep your information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

At our discretion we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## FACEBOOK

Facebook tracking pixel is used by Beyond Gaming.net to help track target demographics on Facebook.  This allows us to promote relevant content and social information through Facebook.  Please refer to our cookies policy for more information regarding your privacy or visit https://www.facebook.net/help/cookies/ for more information.

## GOOGLE

We use Google AdSense, a service for including advertisements from Google Inc. (“Google”).  This service uses ‘cookies’ to track your internet behavior and serve relevant ad content to you.  Adsense also uses Web Beacons to track and evaluate visitor behavior.  Google Analytics is used to evaluate your use of our website and will allow us to determine how to improve user experience.  The information you provide to Google is used subject to Google’s main Privacy Policy. https://www.google.net/policies/privacy/

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

We uphold the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“CalOPPA”) which is the first state law in the United States to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The laws’ reach stretches well beyond California and requires a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites which collect personally identifiable information from Californian consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly what information is being collected and with whom it is being shared and to comply with this policy. Our users can learn more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

## According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

  * users can visit our site anonymously
  * this privacy policy can be found in our footer and is available on the first significant page after entering our website
  * our privacy policy can easily be found and includes the word ‘privacy’
  * users are able to change their personal information by emailing us
  * Children Online Privacy Protection Act

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the United States consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do in order to protect children’s privacy and safety online. More importantly, some games and advertisements represented on our website may not be suitable for children under the age of 13 years. Parental guidance is advised for all children under the age of 13 years.

## Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to comply with the Fair Information Practices Principles, should a data breach occur, we will take responsive action by notifying our users via email within 7 business days. We also agree to the individual redress principle which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires, not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

## CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them and spells out tough penalties for violations. Our vendor will collect your email address in order to market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our users with relevant website content.

In accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act we agree to the following:

  * to NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * to identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * to include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * to monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * to honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * to allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email − if at any time you would like
  * to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence

## Copyright

Beyond Gaming claims no credit for any images posted on this site unless otherwise noted. Images on our website are copyright to its respectful owners.  These rights can fall with the game developers, publisher, producers or any affiliated parties.  In addition, we may obtain images from searches for Creative Commons Licensing to avoid ownership disputes.  However, there might be an instance where we have used an image that holds right.  If you find an image that belongs to you and you do not wish for it to appear on our website then please contact us on sales@Beyond Gaming.net or use our contact form.  We will promptly remove your image and offer our apologies.
